Contact

achaurasia994@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/akashchaurasia-ba2596171 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Engineering Sports Research

Akash Chaurasia

Intern at iNeuron.ai

Vadodara

Summary

As an engineer, I was always fascinated by the world of data and choosing data science as my profession gives me leverage to play with the data and know it. It's been a year since I got my sight on the data science from then onwards, it's become my passion to work on data with the help of different kinds of tools. I also find research as one of the great tools in any form of work, especially, while doing projects. I have good knowledge but I want to learn more and also gain experience, so In future, I can contribute to the community and society.

Experience

iNeuron.ai Intern July 2020 - Present (2 months) Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

Self employed Student August 2017 - Present (3 years 1 month) Vadodara Area, India

Education

Parul University

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Science · (2017 - 2021)